HERE Publications 6199 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Publications
1893-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199 PUBS
14 cubic feet
14 linear ft.
pamphlets, publications.
5840642
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 07, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
5840642
- Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary Golden Jubilee Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Local Joint Executive Board - Cincinnati, Ohio
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 2nd General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union
- Box: 1, Folder: 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 8th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Box: 1, Folder: 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 10th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Box: 1, Folder: 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 11th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Box: 1, Folder: 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 12th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Box: 1, Folder: 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 13th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: June 15
- Box: 1, Folder: 8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 15th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Box: 1, Folder: 9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 16th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Box: 1, Folder: 10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 17th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: July 15
- Box: 1, Folder: 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 18th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Box: 1, Folder: 12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 19th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Box: 1, Folder: 13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 20th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: September 15
- Box: 1, Folder: 14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 21st General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Box: 1, Folder: 15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 22nd General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Box: 1, Folder: 16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 23rd General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Box: 1, Folder: 17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 24th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Box: 1, Folder: 18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Mixer and Server: Proceedings of the 25th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Box: 1, Folder: 19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Proceedings of the 26th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: September 12
- Box: 1, Folder: 20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Proceedings of the 27th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Box: 1, Folder: 21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Catering Industry Employee: Proceedings of the 28th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Box: 1, Folder: 22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 29th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: August
- Box: 1, Folder: 23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Reports of the General President and General Secretary-treasurer, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: April 21
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the 30th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: April
- Box: 1, Folder: 24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Officer's Report to the Thirty-First General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Author: Hugo Ernst and Ed. S. Miller
    Notes: April 4
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the 31st General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance of America and Bartenders International League of America, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Box: 2, Folder: 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 32nd General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Box: 2, Folder: 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 33rd General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Notes: April 20-24
- Box: 2, Folder: 3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 34th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Box: 2, Folder: 4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 35th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Notes: March
- Box: 2, Folder: 5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 36th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 23
  - Item 2: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 36th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 23; Copy 2
- Box: 2, Folder: 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 37th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Notes: June 14
- Box: 2, Folder: 7 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Special Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Notes: December
- Box: 2, Folder: 8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports and Proceedings of the 38th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Notes: May 24
- Box: 2, Folder: 9 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Proposed Constitutional Changes of the 39th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: June 22
  - Item 2: Officers Reports of the 39th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Officers Reports of the 39th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: June 22, Copy 2
  - Item 4: Proceedings of the 39th General Convention of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: June
- Box: 2, Folder: 10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Officers Reports of the 40th General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Author: Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the 40th General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Box: 2, Folder: 11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 41st General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Notes: July
- Box: 2, Folder: 12 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Officer's Reports, Roll Call, Resolutions, Proposed Constitutional Changes, and Daily Proceedings of the 41st General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 8
- Box: 2, Folder: 13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Officer's Reports, Roll Call, Resolutions, Proposed Constitutional Changes, and Daily Proceedings of the 41st General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Notes: July 8; Copy 2
- Box: 2, Folder: 14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the 41st General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Notes: July; Copy 2
- Box: 2, Folder: 15 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Rules and Order of the 42nd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Officers Reports of the 42nd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Proposed Constitutional Amendments: 42nd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Resolution Book #1: 42nd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Box: 3, Folder: 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 42nd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 1 & 2, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 8-9
- Box: 3, Folder: 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 42nd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 3 & 4, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 10-11
- Box: 3, Folder: 3 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Proposed Constitutional Amendments of the 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Notes: July; English and Spanish
- Box: 3, Folder: 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Program Guide for the 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: July; Spanish and English
  - Item 2: Proposed Constitutional Amendments of the 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: July; Spanish and English; Book 2
- Box: 3, Folder: 5 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 1, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Box: 3, Folder: 6 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 1, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Notes: July 15; Copy 2
- Box: 3, Folder: 7 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 2 A.M. Session, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Notes: July 16
- Box: 3, Folder: 8 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 2 A.M. Session, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Notes: July 16; Copy 2
- Box: 3, Folder: 9 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 2 P.M. Session, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Box: 3, Folder: 10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 2 P.M. Session, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Box: 3, Folder: 11 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 3, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: July 17
- Box: 3, Folder: 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 3, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 17; Copy 2
- Box: 3, Folder: 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 4, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Notes: July 18
- Box: 3, Folder: 14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 4 A.M. Session, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Notes: July 18; Copy 2
- Box: 3, Folder: 15 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 4 P.M. Session, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Box: 3, Folder: 16 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 4 P.M. Session, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Box: 3, Folder: 17 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 5, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Notes: July 19
- Box: 4, Folder: 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 43rd General Convention of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union: Day 5, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 19; Copy 2
- Box: 4, Folder: 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution Committee Meeting Session 1, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 11
- Box: 4, Folder: 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Credentials Committee Meeting of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union Session 1, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Notes: July 14
- Box: 4, Folder: 4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Finance Committee Meeting of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes: July 12
- Box: 4, Folder: 5 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Resolutions Committee of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Box: 4, Folder: 6 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Resolutions Committee of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union Session 2, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Notes: July 13
- Box: 4, Folder: 7 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Resolutions Committee of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees International Union Session 3, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Box: 4, Folder: 8 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: September 30, 1939 to December 31, 1946, 1939-1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Box: 4, Folder: 9 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1947 to December 31, 1953, 1947-1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Box: 5, Folder: 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1954 to December 31, 1958, 1954-1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Notes: In effect: June 11
- Box: 5, Folder: 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1959 to December 31, 1962, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Box: 5, Folder: 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1963 to December 31, 1967, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Box: 5, Folder: 4 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1968 to December 31, 1971, 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Box: 5, Folder: 5 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1972 to December 31, 1975, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Box: 5, Folder: 6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1976 to December 31, 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Box: 5, Folder: 7 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement of the Receipts and Expenses of the Hotel employees and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union: January 31, 1980 to September 30, 1984, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Box: 5, Folder: 8 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Notes: June 1
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Notes: June 1; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 9 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Box: 5, Folder: 10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Box: 5, Folder: 11 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Notes: October 15
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Notes: October 15; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 12 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Box: 5, Folder: 13 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Notes: June 15; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 14 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Beverage Dispensers International Alliance, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Box: 5, Folder: 15 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Box: 5, Folder: 16 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Box: 5, Folder: 17 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Notes: October 21
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Notes: October 21; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 18 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 15
  - Item 2: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Notes: February 15; Copy 2
- Box: 5, Folder: 19 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Book of Membership and Constitution of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Notes: June 25